Finding Aid for the The Andrew Nelson Lytle Addition
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series VIII. Writings by Others Box 24
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Riley, H. (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Riley, H. (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Rittenberry, A. (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Rittenberry A. (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Simpson, L. (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Smith, W. (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Southern Partisan (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Sullivan, J. (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Sullivan, W. (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Tate, A. (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Tate, C. (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: [Taylor, P.] (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Tennessee Historical Quarterly (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Wade, J. (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Walsh, W. (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Williams, M. (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Wills, R. (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Wolfe, G. (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Wolfe, G. (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Yoder, E. (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (1 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (2 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (3 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (4 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (5 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (6 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (7 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (8 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (9 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (10 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (11 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (12 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Writings By Others - Unidentified (13 of 13) (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Series X. Fragments
  - Fragments (1 of 4) (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Fragments (2 of 4) (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Fragments (3 of 4) (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Fragments (4 of 4) (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Fragments: Alligator Skin Correspondence Organizer (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Series XI. Envelopes
  - Envelopes (1 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Envelopes (2 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Envelopes (3 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Envelopes (4 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Envelopes (5 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Envelopes (6 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Envelopes (7 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Envelopes (8 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Envelopes (9 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Envelopes (10 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Envelopes (11 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Envelopes (12 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Envelopes (13 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Envelopes (14 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Envelopes (15 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Envelopes (16 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Envelopes (17 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Envelopes (18 of 18) (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Oversize Box 1
  - Writings - Essays: Mirror, Mirror, on the Wall (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Essays: Myth in a Garden (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Agrarians - Publicity Poster, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Family Tree of Andrew Lytle (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Photographs: Alexander, Lamar & Lytle, Andrew (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Photographs: Barker, Judge H. M. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Photographs: Clark, Bill (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Lytle, Edna Pamela (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Family Papers - Certificate from The Daughters of the Confederacy (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Family Papers - Land Deed (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Mills, W.H. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Ralston, Jr., W.H. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Fragments - Publicity Poster for Death of a Salesman (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Fragments - Picture for "Mr. Lytle" by McMahan, J., 1973 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Fragments - Picture for Andrew from "Chauncey", 1936 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Fragments - S. Lux excerpt (Box 29, Folder 16)